Grilling the meat!
Wow.
That's nice.
Wow, that looks good.
What's gone?
Oh, oh, Tongfang.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Pom-pom!
Meat is cooking! Meat is cooking!
Looks delicious! Meat, meat, meat! Meat, meat, meat!
All meat! All meat!
Yay! Horinishi!
Whoo!
It's really good! This! I'm so excited!
Seriously!
Oh, man! Oh, man!
Oh, my God! Smells so good!
It's delicious!
This is fun!
LOL!
Oh, wow!
Mt.
Mt. Fuji
It's out!
Look, look, look.
It's going to burn soon.
Let's go digging.
You've got a cold. It's all over you.
Stones and stuff, don't you think they taste good?
I'm gonna be delicious.
Isn't that great?
It's great.
Wow!
Oh, my God!
This is awesome.
Oh, man.
I'm so happy.
It's like...
It's tiny.
This one's good.
I can eat it now.
I can eat it.
You can eat it.
Wow.
Ooh.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, no.
Yabba.
Oh, man.
Oh, my God, that's good.
Wow, that looks good.
Nick-nick-nick.
I'm starting a tomato casserole.
Tomato casserole, casserole, casserole.
Yum!
Let's eat!Let's eat!
Have you eaten?
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Oh, man!
Yum!
Delicious.
A little sour.
Too good!
It's so sticky, I ate it.
One more time?
One more time.
It's good.
I didn't hear you.
Are you lucky?
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
Is it gone?
It's still there under there.
But it's fading.
I know, right?
I'm worried.
I don't know if it's going away.
I don't want it to go away.
After we eat the meat.
I'm gonna put out the fire one more time.
Maybe we can eat it.
Oh, no.
Too hot, too hot, too hot.
Yeah, too hot.
Wow.
Wow, that's good.
Yum.
Ooh!
Yum!
I'm so happy.
I borrowed this from someone.
Yum!
Did something disappear? It's not gone, is it?
Well, it's still there on the bottom.
Oh!
That's it. Thank you for watching.
Be careful.
[Hajimeji Ending]
Oh, I'm getting a lot of heat right now.
Thank you for watching Gundam Stinger
I'm having a hard time because the fire went out.
The fire went out, but you saved me.
Thank you so much. If I hadn't seen this, I might not have made it.
Oh, it stinks.
It's delicious. It stinks.
Warm.
Pop-pop-pop.
Pop, pop, pop.
Wow.
That's great.
Can you bring me this?
It's got to be hot.If it's not hot
pompon-pompon
That's great.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's it?
Yeah, like that.
That's great.
Good.
After you're done making it.
You're gonna open it, right?
Yeah, I'm gonna open it right up.
Do you want to mix it?
Maybe we can mix it.
Which chopsticks were those?
Oh, here. That's it.
Oh, and one more.
I want to put in some Chinese cabbage.
OK, it's done!
I did it!
That's great!
I always thought it took forever!
Oh, yeah.
Is that the top of Mt. Is that it?
Can we see the top?
I can see the top.
It's still standing.
Mt.
It's bursting!
What?
It's still going strong!
It's real!
What?
It's rupturing.
It's coming out of here.
Oh, no! Oh, my God!
One channel.
Want some?
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
Oh, sorry.
It's good.
Bon appétit.
It's a little blurry.
Is it good?
It's good.
Yummy.
He's cute.
Your nose is less red now.
It's less red now, thank God.
It's delicious.
I can't wait to try it in the pot.
Hey.
Can I come over here?
Yeah, sure.
Sure.
I'll go.
It's not hot in there.
Ooh.
Hot.
Wow.
Looks delicious.Looks delicious
Looks good.
Yay, it's going up!
Oh no, don't look at the color.
I'm eating the rest of the popcorn.
It looks so good!
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's just a little tingle.
It's just up the hill.
Yeah.
First of all, my nose hurts.
Of course it hurts.
It's a little warmer now.
Looks so good!
Tomato casserole.
I hope it's good.
Let's eat.
Let's eat!
Please subscribe to our channel!